gamepop.tv 2013-12-05

# BlueStacks - Privacy

**Bluestack Systems, Inc. Privacy Policy**  
Bluestack Systems, Inc ("Bluestacks") is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy describes Bluestacks policies for collecting, using and disclosing your personal data. By using any of Bluestacks Products you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of (regardless of means of access) any of the current set of products from Bluestacks, collectively referred to as Bluestacks Products, such as the Bluestacks website (bluestacks.com), the Bluestacks App Player for Windows, the Bluestacks App Player for Mac, the Bluestacks Cloud Connect Android app, the GamePop Console, the GamePop Android App, the GamePop iOS App, the FoneLink Android app, the FoneLink iOS app, the FoneLink Web app, the FoneLink Windows 8 app, the BlueStacks Cloud Services, and the Bluestacks Help and Support forum. The Bluestacks Products are owned and provided by Bluestack Systems, Inc.

You can access, download or use Bluestacks Products, through applications on Devices, through APIs, and through third parties. A Device is any computer used to access the Bluestacks Products, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic Device.

Bluestacks Products can enable you to sync information from your Android phone to another Device you own; play applications developed by third parties, individually and collectively referred to as Third Party Apps, on a Device, such as an Android app on a Device running either the Microsoft Windows, Apple OS X or Linux operating systems.

**1) Information we collect from you**

All of the different forms of data, content, and information, including that which can be used to identify an individual, as described below are collectively referred to as Information. We collect Information to provide better services to all of our users from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like how to provide the best user experience for using BlueStacks Products on your particular Device.

We collect Information in two ways:

A) Information you give us: In the course of you using the Bluestacks Products, we may collect Information with your consent that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Information").

When you use FoneLink through your Google account login, we may collect Personal Information such as your name, email address, phone number, and ancillary information such as phone call history, contacts, SMS messages, mobile applications installed on your phone, so that you can view and use such information on other Devices you own.

When you register for a Bluestacks account, we may collect some Personal Information such as your email address, or social networking information if you give us access to your account on social network connection services, or your phone number. You may be asked to choose login Information, such as your email address and a password, which will be used to access your account. You may also provide us ancillary information such as your friends’ email addresses for inviting your friends to use Bluestacks Products or sharing your experience of using such Bluestacks Products with them. If you provide us with Information about another person you represent that you have their permission to do so.

If you contact us via email or our electronic Help Forum, we may collect some Personal Information such as email address and contact information, and also keep your message to respond to your request.

B) Information we get from your use of Bluestacks Products: We (or our service providers acting on our behalf) may collect Information about the Bluestacks Products that you use and how you use them. This information includes information that may identify you as well as statistical information (.Analytics.) that does not identify you. Some Analytics may be correlated with your Personal Information. Usage Information may include:

a) Device Information: We may collect Device-specific Information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique Device identifiers and mobile network Information including phone number). We may associate your Device identifiers or phone number with your Bluestacks Account.

b) Log Information: When you use Bluestacks Products, we may automatically record or log Information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Bluestacks Products. This may include:

  * The Device’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address;
  * Identification numbers associated with your Devices;
  * Device event Information such as crashes, system activity and hardware settings;
  * Locale preferences;
  * Application activity such as app upload, app download, app installation, app uninstallation, app start, app play duration, app stop, app crashes, app network activity and app resource consumption;
  * Date and time stamps associated with transactions;
  * System configuration Information;
  * Metadata concerning your Android apps; and
  * Other interactions with the Bluestacks Products and third party advertisements.

The Bluestacks Products that include websites may also use the following cookies:

  * A cookie which recognizes a user’s browser type, browser language, the date and time of a user’s request and referral URL;
  * A cookie which identifies the web page visited before you came to our website; and
  * A cookie which logs information you search for on our website.

We use cookies to enhance your experience on our website. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored on the hard drive of your computer and are used for record-keeping purposes. Use of cookies facilitates web surfing by performing certain functions.

You may refuse to accept cookies when you are alerted to their existence by us or by activating the setting on your browser, which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our website.

c) Location Information: When you use a location-enabled app, we may collect, process and retain Information about your actual location. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your Device that may, for example, provide Information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers. The location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by us to provide and improve location based products and services. By using a location-enabled app, you consent to us processing Information about your actual location.

d) Third Party App Information: When you download and install Third Party Apps, or when you permit them to be updated, we may record Information about the source, such as the name of the app store or app market, its IP address, the application version number, or any unique application identification number associated with them.

e) Local storage: We may collect Information about storage consumed on your Device by Android apps and their app-specific data.

**2) Children’s Information**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with Personal Information, we take steps to remove such Personal Information and terminate the child’s account unless parental or guardian consent is given.

**3) How We Use Personal Information and Your Choices**

A) Personal Information: Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Bluestacks Products; (ii) to administer your use of the Bluestacks Products; (iii) to personalize and improve your experience; (iv) to provide software updates; (v) to provide you with products, information or services that you request from us or which are related to such requests and we feel may interest you; and (vi) to notify you about changes to Bluestacks Products and services.

B) If you no longer wish to receive promotional emails or text messages from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of those communications.

C) Geo-Location Information: We may use geo-location Information to the greatest extent permitted by law. Some Devices allow applications to access real-time location-based Information (for example, GPS). By using a location-enabled app, you consent to us processing Information about your actual location.

D) Google Analytics: We use the Information to grow our business, to improve or develop our products, to monitor and analyze use of the Bluestacks Products, for the Bluestacks Products’ technical administration, to increase the Bluestacks Products’ functionality and user-friendliness, and to verify users have the authorization needed for the Bluestacks Products to process their requests. To learn more about the privacy policy of Google Analytics, visit http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html. To block the Google Analytics cookie visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

**4) Information Sharing and Disclosure**

A) Your Consent: We may share or disclose your Information to third parties with your consent, for example if you use a third party application to access your account (see below). Through certain features of the Bluestacks Products, you may also have the ability to make some of your Information public. Public Information may be broadly and quickly disseminated.

B) Bluestacks Products Providers, Business Partners and Others: We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Bluestacks Products (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and payment processing). These third parties may have access to your Information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations to adequately safeguard the Information.

C) Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Bluestacks Rights: We may disclose Information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Bluestacks or its users; or (d) protect Bluestacks property rights.

D) Business Transfers: If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your Personal Information, or if it becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

E) Non-private or Non-Personal Information: We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-Personal Information, such as usage statistics of our Bluestacks Products.

**5) Third Parties**

We will not share your Personal Information with our affiliated companies or with third parties who may use it for their marketing purposes without your prior permission.

**6) Data Retention**

We will retain your Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with services or as required by law (whichever is longest). If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your Information to provide you with services, you may delete your account by notifying us. We may retain and use your Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

**7) Bluestacks Community**

Bluestacks Products offer publicly accessible community services such as blogs, forums, and wikis. You should be aware that any Information you provide in these areas might be read, collected and used by others who access them. Your posts may remain even after you cancel your account.

**8) Security**

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. You also play a role in protecting your Information. Please safeguard your user name and password and do not share them with others. If we receive instructions using your login Information we will consider that you have authorized the instructions.

**9) Accessing Your Information**

You may access your account Information to update or delete it or to manage your preferences by visiting the Cloud Connect feature of our application. Please keep your Information up to date and accurate.

**10) Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy at Bluestacks dot com.

**11) Changes to our Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, may provide a more prominent notice (including, for example, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). By continuing to use Bluestacks Products after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by any revised Privacy Policy.

**12) Severability**

If any provisions of this Privacy Policy are found to be void or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed and all other provisions shall remain in force.

**13) Effective Date**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 1, 2012. Last updated May 1, 2013

© 2012, 2013 by Bluestack Systems, Inc. All rights reserved
